다들 줄 서 있네
What’s going on?
왜 같은 것만 가지려고 해?
넌 너면 되잖아 Don’t be Fomo
I’m ‘bout to make you go out of control
On the weekend
It’s time to party
밤은 milky
우린 여기
내 걸음 맞춘 내 속도가 좋아
우리만의 새 길을 만들어
Call me
Skibidi bad bad bad bad bad bad
Light it up
U can dance
U can move
Yes I will dance
예상 밖의 답 나만의 색을 봐
틀려도 멈추지 마
It goes on and on
On the weekend
It’s time to party
밤은 milky
눈부시지
마치 불 같은, 누군간 차가운
전부 다른 빛으로 빛나지
Call me
Skibidi bad bad bad bad bad
Light it up
U can dance
U can move
Yes I will dance
너의 색, 존재감 보여줘
튀는 너의 걸음을 막 걸어 줘
때론 너도 규칙을 깨 so bad
Imma make you never forget what I do
Don’t go waste your time
Celebrate your life
너도 알잖아
선택은 네가 하는 것
Skibidi bad bad bad bad
uh we Light it up
다들 줄 서 있네
What’s going on?
왜 같은 것만 가지려고 해?
넌 너면 되잖아 Don’t be Fomo
I’m ‘bout to make you go out of control
I got money in my bag
I got money for my stash
우린 없는 게 없대
Whaat?
What you know about that
Skibidi bad bad bad bad
uh we Light it up
Skibidi